Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary until
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Wait, he just...
He just broke Captain Kudo's cat claw.
That leaves only five more
of those weird swords.
Don't worry, guys.
He can still fight plenty.
Yeah, he still has another
claw. You can do it!
Rip that Katorea shrimp, Captain Kaido!
Don't use that name anymore.
He doesn't like it, remember?
I think in this village his
name is Kla-ha... something.
Kla-ha something! Yeah! Kla-ha
something! Get him! Good!
Shut your mouths!
All of you!
Come out, you brats!
I know you're hiding!
Give yourselves up!
Come over here and we'll take you to her!
Just don't kill us!
Do you think I'm stupid?
I won't fall for that, you silly rugrats.
Oh, damn it.
We got him! No!
Pepper attack!
Achoo!
End of the line, hypnotist!
Looks like you bit off a little
more than you could chew.
No!
We failed!
Real pirates don't take kindly to
being mocked by the likes of you!
Onion!
You pretend, pirates.
Sure got in over your heads, didn't you?
Rich girl, I know you're here. Listen!
Unless you show yourself, I'll
execute these three little lambs.
and I will make sure to do
it in a most painful fashion.
Do not doubt my skill at such a task.
There you are.
Miss Kaya, run for your life!
Hey.
Yeah, that's them, all right.
They're the other way.
Soon enough, I'll deal with you.
In the only appropriate
manner, extermination.
I'll also kill that full jungle.
But why kill us, captain?
Come on, please don't
talk around like that.
Captain, guru, it's still not too late
for us to attack the village, right?
Yeah.
And if captain jungle gets her to write,
her will, then your plan
should still work perfectly.
This plan is no longer
any of your concern.
When all of you are dead, this village
will know who to blame for this atrocity.
I never intended to let any of you
mongrels leave this village alive.
No one.
Who knows my true identity can be
allowed to live to tell about it.
No way.
You had already planned to kill every
last one of us from the very beginning.
That's right.
Three years ago, I planned
to erase Captain Kaido.
And every last person who ever knew him.
It's all part of my plan.
You guys are dumb.
You're the most Uncle pirates I know.
We're Uncle, huh?
Pirates are nothing more than savages.
Incapable of rising above
their animal nature!
Without my plans, what could
they possibly accomplish?
A crew is nothing to me.
They are simply a means to an end.
Crew members are just pawns
in the captain's game.
Whether my men live or die
is up to me and me alone.
If I tell them to fight, they will fight.
And if I order them to
die, they had better do it.
They know the punishment for disobedience.
This is how pirates are!
Don't you dare talk down to me, boy!
You know,
no matter how many hundreds or thousands
of men follow you as their captain,
you will never be as good as Usopp.
You fool.
Are you saying that I am inferior to a kid
pretending to be a pirate? That's right.
Well, aren't you funny?
Don't get all cocky just because
you snapped off one of my cat claws.
How exactly is he better than me?
Let's hear it.
Cause he's got heart.
He's got what?
A guy like you doesn't
know what a true pirate is.
Impossible!
He kept up with the pussyfoot maneuver!
How insulting.
It would appear that you need a
lesson in what real pirates are like.
It's not pleasant.
Your first lesson will be about terror.
A lesson I learned well
as I stared down death.
Hey, should he be in that stance?
No, this is bad!
Why is he using that technique?
He's only fighting one guy.
There's no reason to use
the out-of-the-back attack!
This isn't a good spot for us.
I mean, he can get us, too.
Yeah, he did say he was
going to kill us all earlier.
Please, Captain Kaido,
anything but that technique!
We'll do anything, Captain!
Please, Captain Kaido!
What's the big deal?
He's just wobbling back and forth.
Out of the back attack!
What a small haul!
You know, I really thought they'd
have more treasure than this.
Let's see if the boy hasn't
finished this fight yet.
What?
Everyone has stopped.
Is it over?
What's he doing over there?
That guy's everywhere!
Don't do this, Captain!
Please stop! We're dead!
We can't reason with the
doubt that he's started!
His sidestead maneuver is so fast,
not even he knows what he's cutting!
But how could he have killed
so many of us without even...
No!
What's happening out there?
People are just getting cut to ribbons!
Shoo yourself!
Butler!
Don't you have any honor?
Those men are your friends!
Reef.
I found you!
You bastard.
You should have accepted
your fate like a good boy.
Now look what you've done.
Thanks to you, my little
pawns are still alive.
And in misery.
it would have been better just
to let them die in the attack.
So now what?
Do you have something to say? Yeah.
No matter what happens to me.
I will never be like you.
Not will.
Someone like you can't be like me.
You see?
You are going to die here today.
There's no need for that.
Please, leave the children be.
I'll write the will.
No! Kaya!
He's gonna kill you as soon
as you write that will!
Silly girl.
Don't you know you can't bargain with me?
Captain Kuro specifically instructed
me to get rid of everyone.
No!
If you don't do exactly as I say,
then you won't get to kill me!
Ant, I won't write my will! Hold
on! Hold on! Just calm down!
Don't be so hasty!
I absolutely have to get
you to write that will!
Stop! Kaya!
Alright, fine, I'll let
the little brats go.
But in their condition, they won't
be making too quick of a getaway.
Don't forget to sign your name I know
I leave my entire
fortune to my butler.
Clad or yes very good this is your
wheel all right excellent work now.
Remember we had a deal you promised me
you wouldn't kill them
just relax I know I.
I may not look like it, but
I'm regarded as an honest man.
Kaya!
There!
Step on it!
Go, go, go!
Come on!
Let's go!
Let's go! Over there!
I can't help him out!
That's enough of that hypno-freak!
Let the girl go! Damn it!
Looks like I was followed.
I guess I'd better finish off
the rich girl quickly, then.
That was simply a war.
The real fight begins now.
Soon I will be feasting on your feet,
complimented by the sweet wine of your agony.
Now!
Out of the back attack!
Nice try, you jerk! Damn you!
Get away from me!
Wow, Butler man, right now
your life really sucks.
Your plan of three years is
a complete and total failure.
Let go!
Hey, look, that weird
kid called Captain Kuro.
I don't believe it.
If that goofy kid manages to beat him,
then that means Captain Kuro won't
be able to slaughter us, right?
It's time to die.
Oh, no, you don't!
Stupid snot-nosed brat!
Ha!
Looks like you're one
step too late, swordsman!
Wouldn't say that!
Excellent!
That branch was getting
in the way of my shot!
What?
Help me, Usopp!
Do it, Captain!
Eat this, hypnotist!
Yeah!
Get him, you crazy rubber guy!
You're going dead, you mean bastard!
Get off me!
Shut up!
You have no right to cheer me on!
Let go of me!
Now, time for the exploding star!
You insect!
My spirit will absolutely
not be disrupted!
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure!
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me!
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me!
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go!
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true!
But if the world ever changes?
I call out your name!
We return to the time when
everything's the same!
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?